belisi.com 2011-01-16

# Belisi Reviews, Belisi Service, Belisi Policies - Privacy Notice

Belisi Privacy Notice

Last updated: August 20, 2009

Belisi values your privacy. We know that you care about how information about you is used when you provide it at Belisi.com. We appreciate your trust. By visiting Belisi.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

What Personal Information About Customers Does Belisi.com Collect?

The information we learn from our customers helps us personalize your shopping experience at Belisi.com. Here are the types of information we gather.

Information You Submit at Belisi.com: We receive and store any information you enter on Belisi.com, including email address, or give to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of the features offered on Belisi.com. We use the information that you provide to respond to your requests, customize your shopping experience, make improvements to our services and communicate with you.

Email A Friend. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Belisi Fashions does not store this information.

Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us at Belisi.com, like many other web sites, we use cookies and we obtain certain types of information when you point your web browser to Belisi.com. It is possible to use certain tools to block cookies; however, if you choose to use these tools, we won't be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Belisi.com.

E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful to you, we often receive confirmation by using Web beacons when you open or click on a link in an email from Belisi.com. See "What are Cookies and other Tracking Utilities?" If you would like to adjust your e-mail preferences, please visit your "My Account" and change your preferences. You may also unsubscribe to any promotional email by following the instructions included in each email.

Information from Other Sources: We may receive information about you from a third party service provider such as a credit reporting agency and add it to your account information stored in the Belisi database.

Contacting you via Cellular Phone: We will only contact you via your cellular phone if you provide your cellular phone number to us.

What types of email communications does Belisi.com send?

Administrative emails related to your orders: If you place an order at Belisi.com, we will send you emails related to that order. For example, telling you when the order has been shipped or if you request a refund, when that refund has been processed. If you wish, you may opt-out of receiving these administrative emails by changing your preferences in "My Account".

Use of Data Collected

We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data for marketing and promotional purposes, send SMS alerts or notification, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future telemarketing, SMS text-messaging, e-mails or postal mailings. By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your number is found on a do not call registry, in-house list or similar registry.

Blog subscriptions & special reports: Belisi publishes blogs and sometimes publishes special reports about fashion. If you specifically request to receive these communications, we will send them to you. Any advertisements placed in these blog emails are for products sold by Belisi Fashions, Inc. and again, we don't offer advertising to 3rd parties.

How do I opt-out from receiving email communications?

Opt-out link in emails: In all emails we send there is an opt-out link. If you click the opt-out link, you will be opted-out from the type of email in which you've clicked the link. For example, if you click the opt-out link from one of the blog update emails, you will not longer get the blog update email, but you will still continue to receive administrative emails about your account.

How do I opt-out from SMS text messaging?

For SMS text messages, you may remove your information by replying "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received and we will remove your personal information within 10 days of receiving such request.

Your account at Belisi.com: If you have an account at Belisi.com, you can change your email preferences and account information (including email address) by clicking 'Edit My Account'. You'll be taken to a page in which you can see all the various types of emails we send and choose subscribe or unsubscribe as you wish. You may update or delete any account information at 'Edit My Account' as well. Once your preferences are set, simply click the 'Save' button.

Call our customer service center: If you would rather talk to a person, you can call 1-800-434-1962 and one of our customer service representative can opt you out of any emails you choose. Our hours of operation are Monday through Friday Eastern Standard Time.

Send us a letter: In accordance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all of our emails have our postal address at the bottom. It is PO Box 689620, Jupiter, FL 33468-9620. If you send a letter to our office, including the email address you want unsubscribed, we will follow your instructions.

Contact us form: You can send us an email through our online form. Click here to contact us.

What are Cookies and Other Tracking Utilities?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that Belisi transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide personalized product recommendations and other personalized features. For this reason, we ties your personally identifiable information to our cookies. While your browser will allow you to disable cookies, we recommend that you leave them turned on so that you can enjoy the best possible experience at Belisi.com. Some of our business partners (ie tracking utility company) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these third party cookies.

Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics to enhance our Web site.

Web Beacons

We employ a software technology called Web beacons, that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, Web beacons are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We use clear gifs in our HTML- based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. For this reason, we tie your email address to the Web beacons. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see follow the unsubscribe instructions in each email or change your email preferences in My Account.

Does Belisi.com Share the Information It Receives?

Third-Party Service Providers: Belisi employs other companies and individuals to perform various functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, SMS text message, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing various marketing services, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but they may not use it for any other purpose.

Google Checkout: You also have the option to use Google Checkout when on site and completing an order. When you use this option, please be aware that you will be taken to Google’s own site to finish the purchase. Google’s privacy policy governs the collection and use of the information that you provide to them while on their site.

Links to Other Sites: This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Belisi Fashions. Please be aware that we, Belisi Fashions, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information, generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Belisi Fashions or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

As Directed by Law: Belisi Fashions will release account information and other personal information when we believe such release is required in order to comply with the law, enforce our conditions of use, or protect the rights, property or safety or Belisi.com, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Can I have access to my personal information?

Belisi will provide you reasonable access to your personally identifiable information, including email address, at no cost to you, within 30 days of your access request. If we cannot provide access within the 30-day period, we will tell you when we will provide access. In the unlikely event that we cannot provide you access to this information, we will explain why we cannot do so. To request access to your personally identifying information, click here to contact us or write us at the following address:

PO Box 689620

Jupiter, FL 33468-9620

How Secure is Information About Me on Belisi.com?

Belisi works to protect the security of your information, including email address, during transmission to us by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. SSL encrypts the information you submit online. Please be aware, however, that no transmission of information via the Internet can be entirely secure. You should, therefore, always use caution when submitting personal information online. We take commercially reasonable steps to provide security for your information once we receive it.

Are Children Allowed to Use Belisi.com?

Belisi does not sell products for purchase by children. At present we do not sell children’s products; however, in the future, we may sell children’s products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may only use Belisi.com with the involvement of a parent or guardian. We do not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13.

Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Belisi.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Florida. If you are concerned about privacy at Belisi.com, please contact us and we will attempt to address your concerns.

Blog

If you use a blog or upload photos/comments on our site you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. When you go to our blog, please note that it is hosted by a third party. Web pages within its frame may appear to be on www. belisi.com when the user is still on a third party Web site. Our privacy policy governs the collection and use of any information submitted while on our blog.

Testimonials & Photos

From time to time, we publish testimonials & photographs on our site. By submitting photos, testimonials to us either through Belisi.com or to our customer service department you are providing royalty-free, unlimited consent to Belisi to modify and publish the content you have submitted to Belisi.com or other Belisi owned website properties.

Reviews

Belisi.com has arranged with PowerReviews, Inc. (d/b/a Buzzillions) ("PowerReviews") to facilitate the collection of reviews on products sold on Belisi.com. When you submit a product review to Belisi.com, you are also agreeing to the terms of use and privacy policies of Buzzillions. Your reviews may be posted on both Belisi.com and Buzzillions.com.

Changes in this Privacy Statement

Our business at Belisi is constantly changing. Over time, our Privacy Notice and Conditions of Use will change as well. Unless otherwise stated, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information and/or email practices regarding information that we have about you and your account. We value the trust you place in us when you shop at Belisi.com. If we change this privacy statement in ways that affect the personally identifying information we have collected through our Sites, we will post those changes in this space and advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes. We will also post a prominent notice on our home page that this privacy statement has changed.
